{"data":[{"question":"I am sure you would find a suitable applicant to fill the vacancy.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"sure","b":"would find","c":"suitable","d":"to fill","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Would find-> will find","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"The rough sea made the ferry be unable to sail.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The rough sea","b":"made","c":"be unable","d":"to sail","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Be unable-> unable","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"The destroy of the old city London in 1600s was caused by a fire.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"destroy","b":"city","c":"in","d":"was caused","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Destroy-> destruction","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"The spectators were moved with tears when they saw the Prince to kill himself.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were moved","b":"with tears","c":"when","d":"to kill","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- With tears-> in tears","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"You can borrow the book from him if you promise to keep it cleanly.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"borrow","b":"from","c":"to keep","d":"cleanly","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Cleanly-> clean","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"It is be important that your brother should stop smoking at once.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"be important","b":"that","c":"smoking","d":"at once","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Be important-> is important","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"The policeman ordered the children not to playing football in the street.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"ordered","b":"the children","c":"not to playing","d":"in the street","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Not to playing-> not to play","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Another attempt to climb that mountain will be done next year.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Another attempt","b":"to climb that mountain","c":"will be done","d":"next year","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Will be done-> will be made","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"It's wrong of you giving her a chance to talk.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"wrong","b":"of","c":"giving","d":"to talk","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Giving-> to give","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"If the atmosphere is polluted, the solar energy that reaching the earth may be dangerous.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is polluted","b":"energy","c":"reaching","d":"may be","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Reaching-> reaches","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"}]}